(Raj:)Cinnamon's here for her sleepover party.
(Howard:)You know if you had a stroke,
she'd eat you, right?
(Raj:)And it would be my pleasure
to be her num-num.
(Howard:)Okay, so, what do I need to know
to take care of her?
(Raj:)It's very simple.
For breakfast, she has an egg white frittata.
(Raj:)Give her a choice of home fries
or an English muffin.
(Raj:)But not both. We're watching our weight.
(Raj:)Uh, for dinner, something simple, a veal chop,
some scampi, whatever you like.
- Classy dog.
- Yes.
(Raj:)Also, don't forget to close the toilet
or she'll drink out of it.
I feel for you. Heh.
(Howatd:)I've got a psychotic mommy too.
(Sheldon(off):)Leonard, are you in bed?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon(off):)Me too.